	questionList = questionList.concat([
	
	//Future  3
	{question:"The boy will eat.", answers:["El niño va a comer.", "El niño comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comerá.", answers:["The boy will eat.", "The child will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be an apple.", answers:["Será una manzana.", "Va a ser una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será una manzana.", answers:["It will be an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Será una mujer.", answers:["It will be a woman.","She will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be a woman.", answers:["Será una mujer.", "Va a ser una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella será una mujer.", answers:["She will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She will be a woman.", answers:["Será una mujer.", "Ella será una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted será una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serás una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serás una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be a woman.", answers:["Usted será una mujer.", "Tú serás una mujer.", "Serás una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a girl.", answers:["Será una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a child.", answers:["Será una niña.", "Será un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted será un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serás un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serás un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be a man.", answers:["Usted será un hombre.", "Tú serás un hombre.", "Serás un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a boy.", answers:["Será un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será un niño.", answers:["It will be a boy.", "He will be a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be a man.", answers:["Será un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será un hombre.", answers:["He will be a man.", "It will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él será un hombre.", answers:["He will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He will be a man.", answers:["Será un hombre.", "Él será un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comerá.", answers:["The man will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man will eat.", answers:["El hombre comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú beberás agua.", answers:["You will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will drink water.", answers:["Tú beberás agua.", "Beberás agua.", "Usted beberá agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo comeré.", answers:["I will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I will eat.", answers:["Comeré.","Yo comeré."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño beberá.", answers:["A boy will drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy will drink.", answers:["Un niño beberá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo beberé.", answers:["I will drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I will drink.", answers:["Yo beberé.", "Beberé."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comerás.", answers:["You will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will eat.", answers:["Tú comerás.", "Comerás.", "Usted comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será pan.", answers:["It will be bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be bread.", answers:["Será pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será agua.", answers:["It will be water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be water.", answers:["Será agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You will be men.", answers:["Ustedes serán hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serán hombres.", answers:["You will be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Seremos hombres.", answers:["We will be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will be men.", answers:["Seremos hombres.", "Nosotros seremos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seremos mujeres.", answers:["We will be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will be women.", answers:["Nosotras seremos mujeres.", "Seremos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberemos leche.", answers:["We will drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberemos leche.", answers:["We will drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will drink milk.", answers:["Beberemos leche.", "Nosotros beberemos leche.", "Nosotras beberemos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberemos agua.", answers:["We will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberemos agua.", answers:["We will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will drink water.", answers:["Beberemos agua.", "Nosotros beberemos agua.", "Nosotras beberemos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be women.", answers:["Ustedes serán mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serán mujeres.", answers:["You will be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras seremos mujeres.", answers:["We will be women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will be women.", answers:["Nosotras seremos mujeres.","Seremos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas serán mujeres.", answers:["They will be women."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They will be women.", answers:["Ellas serán mujeres.","Serán mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You will drink water.", answers:["Tú beberás agua.", "Beberás agua.", "Usted beberá agua.", "Ustedes beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beberán agua.", answers:["You will drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellos serán hombres.", answers:["They will be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will be men.", answers:["Ellos serán hombres.", "Serán hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will drink milk.", answers:["Tú beberás leche.","Beberás leche.","Usted beberá leche.","Ustedes beberán leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros seremos hombres.", answers:["We will be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will be men.", answers:["Nosotros seremos hombres.","Seremos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They will drink.", answers:["Beberán.","Ellos beberán.","Ellas beberán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beberán.", answers:["They will drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beberán agua.", answers:["The girls will drink water.","The children will drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls will drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beberán agua.", answers:["The boys will drink water.","The children will drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys will drink water.", answers:["Los niños beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribirás un libro.", answers:["You will write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will write a book.", answers:["Tú escribirás un libro.","Escribirás un libro.","Usted escribirá un libro.","Ustedes escribirán un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribirá un libro.", answers:["You will write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribiré una carta.", answers:["I will write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I will write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribiré una carta.","Escribiré una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribiremos un libro.", answers:["We will write a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We will write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribiremos un libro.","Nosotras escribiremos un libro.","Escribiremos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beberán vino.", answers:["They will drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They will drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beberán vino.","Ellos beberán vino.","Beberán vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I will drink wine.", answers:["Yo beberé vino.","Beberé vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo beberé vino.", answers:["I will drink wine."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú leerás el libro.", answers:["You will read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will read the book.", answers:["Tú leerás el libro.","Leerás el libro.","Usted leerá el libro.","Ustedes leerán el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribirán.", answers:["The girls will write.","The children will write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls will write.", answers:["Las niñas escribirán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella será una persona.", answers:["She will be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She will be a person.", answers:["Ella será una persona.","Será una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leeré.", answers:["I will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will read.", answers:["Yo leeré.","Leeré."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leerá.", answers:["The boy will read.","The child will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy will read.", answers:["El niño leerá."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él será una persona.", answers:["He will be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He will be a person.", answers:["Él será una persona.","Será una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leeremos un diario.", answers:["We will read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will read a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leeremos un diario.","Nosotras leeremos un diario.","Leeremos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leerán.", answers:["They will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will read.", answers:["Ellas leerán.","Ellos leerán.","Leerán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leerán un libro.", answers:["They will read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will read a book.", answers:["Ellas leerán un libro.","Ellos leerán un libro.","Leerán un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comeremos arroz.", answers:["We will eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comeremos arroz.", answers:["We will eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comeremos arroz.","Nosotros comeremos arroz.","Comeremos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaré pescado.", answers:["I will cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaré pescado.","Cocinaré pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comerán nada.", answers:["They will not eat anything.","They won't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comerán nada.","Ellas no comerán nada.","No comerán nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaré.", answers:["I will not cook.","I won't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocinaré.","No cocinaré."], language:"Spanish"}
	
	]);
